{
    "subject": "resource/Joan_Maragall",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Spain",
    "human_readable": "Joan Maragall was born in Spain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9518146514892578,
            "question": "Is Joan Maragall from Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9164193868637085,
            "question": "Was Joan Maragall Spanish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.885057270526886,
            "question": "Where was Joan Maragall born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6856428384780884,
            "question": "What country is associated with Joan Maragall's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6762133240699768,
            "question": "In which country did Joan Maragall originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6691015362739563,
            "question": "What nationality is Joan Maragall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6175063848495483,
            "question": "Can you tell me Joan Maragall's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6047604084014893,
            "question": "Where was Joan Maragall raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43993863463401794,
            "question": "Spain is known as the birthplace of who?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3992370069026947,
            "question": "To which nation does Joan Maragall belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joan Maragall was born in Spain.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4913_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Spain is known as the birthplace of who?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4913_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Joan Maragall raised?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4913_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me Joan Maragall's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4913_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4913_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4913_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4913_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4913_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4913_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4913_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4913_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4913_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4913_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4913_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to the documents, Joan Maragall was indeed born in Barcelona, Spain (1860)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Joan Maragall was born and raised in Barcelona, Spain, which supports the statement that he was born in Spain."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}